Finding Aid for Kelsey Museum of Archaeology papers 1890-1987
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Francis Willey Kelsey papers, 1890-1927; 65.5 linear feet
  - Educational Institutions
    - University of Michigan
      - Clubs and Associations
        - Club Plays
          - The Menaechmi
            - Re: libretto and music, 1916 (Box 54, Folder 3)
            - Press notices; reviews, 1916 (Box 54, Folder 4)
          - Iphigenia
            - Miscellaneous material, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 5)
            - Chorus parts, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 6)
            - Photographs, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 7)
            - Press notices, reviews, 1917 (Box 54, Folder 8)
          - The Phormio of Terence
            - Miscellaneous material, 1918 (Box 55, Folder 1)
          - The Much Woo'd Maiden
            - Miscellaneous material, 1919 (Box 55, Folder 2)
          - Helena's Husband
            - Miscellaneous material, 1920 (Box 55, Folder 3)
          - The Miser
            - Script, 1921 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Clubs, Miscellaneous, 1913-1923
        - League of Nations Non-Partisan Association, 1923 (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - Research Club, 1913-1919 (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - Student Christian Association, 1922 (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - University Club, 1915 (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - Committee on Humanistic Publications, 1916 (Box 55, Folder 6)
        - Committee, Normal College, 1914 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Deans
        - Bursley, J.A. and Cabot, Hugh, 1923; 1926 (Box 55, Folder 7)
        - Effinger, John R.
          - 1911-1915 (Box 55, Folder 8)
          - 1916-1919 (Box 55, Folder 9)
          - 1921-1926 (Box 55, Folder 10)
        - Guthe Carl E.
          - 1913-1915 (Box 55, Folder 11)
          - 1922-1926 (Box 55, Folder 12)
        - Kraus, Edward H., 1911-1913; 1916; 1918; 1921-1926 (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - Lloyd, Alfred H.
          - 1911-1913 (Box 56, Folder 2)
          - 1917-1918 (Box 56, Folder 3)
          - 1919-1921 (Box 56, Folder 4)
          - 1922-1923 (Box 56, Folder 5)
          - 1924-1927 (Box 56, Folder 6)
        - Reed John 0., 1908; 1910-1912; 1915 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Departments-Latin
        - Teachers' Outlines of Courses, 1881; 1889; 1894; 1910-1914 (Box 56, Folder 8)
        - Teachers' Reports
          - 1891-1900 (Box 56, Folder 9)
          - 1900-1910, 1911-1912; 1916-1917 (Box 56, Folder 10)
        - Exams and Caesar Exams, 1895-1897; 1900 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - Teachers, 1922 (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - Re: lectures, 1913-1914 (Box 57, Folder 3)
        - Re: Caesar, 1920-1921 (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - Order of examination, degrees granted, 1890; 1893-1894; 1896-1901; 1903-1913; 1922 (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - Y and Z, 1914; 1921 (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - Questionnaires, 1922; 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 7-8)
        - Class register, 1917-1918 (Box 57, Folder 9)
        - Fellowships, 1914-1923; 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 10)
        - Class Records, Summer Session, 1890-1925 (Box 58)
        - Budget, 1893-1924; 4 folders (Box 59, Folder 1)
          - 1893-1900 (Box 59, Folder 1)
          - 1900-1910 (Box 59, Folder 2)
          - 1911-1915 (Box 59, Folder 3)
          - 1916-1924 (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - Requisitions-duplicates, 1914 (Box 59, Folder 5)
        - U/M Financial Report, 1917-1918; 2 folders (Box 59, Folder 6-7)
        - Purchasing Orders
          - 1915-1916 (Box 59, Folder 8)
          - 1916-1919 (Box 60)
      - Other Departments
        - Education, Hospital, Museum of Zoology, Theater, 1914-1926 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Music
        - Greek music
          - 1896, 1898-1899; 1911; 1915 (Box 61, Folder 2)
          - The Sapphic Stanza by J.S. Tunison, 1896 (Box 61, Folder 3)
          - Fragments De L'Eneide en Musique by Jules Combarieu, 1898 (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - Moore, Earl V., 1921-1923; 1927 (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - Sink, Charles A.
          - 1910-1911 (Box 61, Folder 5)
          - 1912-1913 (Box 61, Folder 6)
          - 1914-1915 (Box 61, Folder 7)
          - 1916-1917 (Box 61, Folder 8)
          - 1918-1919 (Box 61, Folder 9)
          - 1920-1921 (Box 62, Folder 1)
          - 1922 (Box 62, Folder 2)
          - 1923-1924 (Box 62, Folder 3)
          - 1920-1927 (Box 62, Folder 4)
        - Stanley, Albert A.
          - 1907, 1911; 1913-1919 (Box 62, Folder 5)
          - 1920-1921 (Box 62, Folder 6)
          - 1922 (Box 62, Folder 7)
          - 1923 (Box 62, Folder 8)
          - 1924-1927 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Extension Service
        - Henderson, William D.
          - 1911-1919 (Box 62, Folder 10)
          - 1921-1923, 1925-1926 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Library
        - Belser, Amanda, 1916-1919; 1924 (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - Bishop, William W.
          - 1914-1915 (Box 63, Folder 2)
          - 1916 (Box 63, Folder 3)
          - 1917, 4 folders (Box 63, Folder 4)
          - 1918-1919, 4 folders (Box 63, Folder 5)
          - 1924-1927 (Box 63, Folder 6)
        - Brown, Raymond N. and Finney, Byron A., 1911-1912; 1916-1918 (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Goodrich, Francis L.D.
          - 1910-1914 (Box 63, Folder 8)
          - 1915-1918, 1921-1926 (Box 63, Folder 9)
        - Koch, Theodore W.
          - 1908, 1910-1912 (Box 63, Folder 10)
          - 1913-1914, 2 folders (Box 63, Folder 11)
          - 1915, 1917-1919 (Box 63, Folder 12)
        - Library Committee, 1924-1925 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Michigan Union
        - Cards, bills, etc., 1913-1919 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Presbyterian Association
        - Blueprints and Correspondence, 1921-1922 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Presidents
        - Angell, James B., 1900; 1903-1904; 1910-1914; 1919; 1921-1927 (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Burton, Marion L., 1920-1925; 5 folders (Box 64, Folder 4-8)
        - Hutchins, Harvey B.
          - 1907, 1910-1911 (Box 64, Folder 9)
          - 1912-1913 (Box 64, Folder 10)
        - Hutchins, Harvey B.
          - 1915 (Box 65, Folder 1)
          - 1916-1917 (Box 65, Folder 2-3)
          - 1918 (Box 65, Folder 4)
          - 1919-1920 (Box 65, Folder 5)
          - 1922-1927 (Box 65, Folder 6)
        - Little, Clarence, 1925-1927 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Purchasing Agent
        - Christensen, J.C., 1914-1927
          - 1914-1929 (Box 65, Folder 8)
          - 1920-1923 (Box 65, Folder 9)
          - 1924-1927 (Box 65, Folder 10)
        - Loos, C.L., 1913-1914 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Registrar
        - Hall, Arthur G., 1911-1914; 1916-1919; 1922-1924 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Secretary
        - Buckley, Paul, 1924-1926 (Box 66, Folder 2)
        - Smith, Shirley W., 1909-1926
          - 1909-1911 (Box 66, Folder 3)
          - 1912-1913 (Box 66, Folder 4)
          - 1914-1915 (Box 66, Folder 5)
          - 1916-1917 (Box 66, Folder 6)
          - 1918-1919 (Box 66, Folder 7)
          - 1920-1922 (Box 66, Folder 8)
          - 1923-1926 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Superintendent
        - Marks, J.H., 1910-1916 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Treasurer
        - Campbell, R. A., 1913-1915; 1918; 1920-1922; 1924-1926 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Other Schools
      - Utica Normal and Industrial Institute
        - General correspondence
          - 1913, 1915-1919 (Box 66, Folder 12)
          - 1920-1924, 1926 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Voorhees Industrial School
        - General Correspondence, 1913-1919; 1922-1923; 1925 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Joint Projects/Special Projects
    - Humanistic Series
      - Correspondence
        - Freer, Charles
          - 1907-1913, 8 folders (Box 67, Folder 1-8)
          - 1914-1919, 9 folders (Box 68, Folder 1-9)
          - Kennedy, J.M., 1908-1909 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Freer Manuscripts
        - Agreements with estimates, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 1)
        - Plan of work and publication, Henry Sanders, 1908-1909 (Box 69, Folder 2)
        - Dennison, Walter, 1909 (Box 69, Folder 3)
        - Foreign Correspondence, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 4)
        - American Correspondence, 1908-1909 (Box 69, Folder 5)
        - Ramsey, W. C., 1913-1914 (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - Research and Publication memo, undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - Statements and contract, 1912-1914 (Box 69, Folder 8)
        - Expenses, 1907-1914 (Box 69, Folder 9)
        - Vouchers returned, 1914-1915; 1919 (Box 69, Folder 10)
        - Chinese glazes report, 1914 (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - J.S. Cushing & Company, 1916-1917 (Box 69, Folder 12)
        - Committee on Humanistic Publications, 1914-1916 (Box 69, Folder 13)
        - Catalogs listing Humanistic Publications
          - 1913 (Box 69, Folder 14)
          - 1918-1919 (Box 69, Folder 15)
        - The Michigan Alumnus, 1913 (Box 69, Folder 16)
        - De Cou, Herbert Fletcher, 1908-1911 (Box 69, Folder 17)
        - Loeb, James, 1908-1912
          - 1908-1909 (Box 69, Folder 18)
          - 1910-1912 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Expeditions
      - Cyrene
        - Norton, Richard
          - 1906, 1909-August 1911 (Box 70, Folder 1)
          - September-December 1911 (Box 70, Folder 2)
          - 1912 (Box 70, Folder 3)
        - Norton, Richard Reports, 1910-1912 (Box 70, Folder 4)
        - Reports to Arthur Fairbanks, 1910-1911 (Box 70, Folder 5)
        - Reports to Kelsey, Gardner Lane, 1911-1912 (Box 70, Folder 6)
        - Armour, Allison V., 1909-1912 (Box 70, Folder 7)
        - Brooks, Noah W., 1911 (Box 70, Folder 8)
        - Fairbanks, Arthur, 1909-1913 (Box 70, Folder 9)
          - 1909 (Box 69, Folder 9)
          - October 1910-June 1911 (Box 69, Folder 10)
          - July 1911-January 1913 (Box 69, Folder 11)
        - Hoppin, Joseph C., 1910-1912 (Box 70, Folder 12)
        - Lane, Gardner, 1908-1912; 3 folders
          - 1908-1909 (Box 70, Folder 13)
          - 1910-April 1911 (Box 70, Folder 14)
          - May 1911-1912 (Box 70, Folder 15)
        - Department of State, 1910-1912; 2 folders
          - December 1910-September 1911 (Box 71, Folder 1)
          - October 1911-July 1912 (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - General Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 71, Folder 3)
        - Cyrene Indemnity Fund, 1913-1914 (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - Cyrene Plates and photos, 1911-1912 (Box 71, Folder 5)
        - Cyrene newspaper clippings, 1911-1912 (Box 71, Folder 6)
        - Cyrene miscellaneous items including plates, 1911 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Near East
        - Patmos
          - Father Gerassimos, 1921-1922 (Box 71, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence, 1920-1922 (Box 71, Folder 9)
          - Photograph and floor plan, 1921 (Box 71, Folder 10)
          - Notes made while on the is, 1919-1920 (Box 71, Folder 11)
          - Miscellaneous Notes I, 1920 (Box 71, Folder 12)
          - Miscellaneous Notes II, circa 1920 (Box 71, Folder 13)
          - Patmos manuscript for the National Geographic, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
            (8 prints)
          - Patmos views for the National Geographic, undated (Box 72, Folder 2)
            (11 prints)
          - Miscellaneous papers, 1922 (Box 72, Folder 3)
          - Photographs, undated; 3 folders (Box 72, Folder 4-6)
          - Maps, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
          - Angora Concession, 1923-1924 (Box 73, Folder 1)
          - Miscellaneous material, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 2)
        - Antioch of Pisidia
          - Swain's reports, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 3)
          - Catalogue of photographs, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 4)
          - Lists of photographs, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 5)
          - Turkish conditions, undated (Box 73, Folder 6)
          - Sketch plans, 1926 (Box 73, Folder 7)
          - Maps, printed, 1925 (Box 73, Folder 8)
          - Illustrations, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 9)
          - News clippings, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 10)
          - Miscellaneous, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 11)
          - Categories I, 1924-1926 (Box 73, Folder 12)
          - Categories II, 1924-1925 (Box 73, Folder 12)
          - Publications re: Patmos, undated (Box 74)
          - Publications re: Eng, undated (Box 75)
          - Publications re: Germany, undated (Box 76)
          - Publications and Correspondence re: Balkans, undated
            - Bucharest, 1919-1920 (Box 77, Folder 1)
            - Sophia, circa 1920 (Box 77, Folder 2)
          - Turkish Treaty and outline on memoranda on Near East, Chiefly First Expedition (Box 78, Folder 1)
            - American Relief and mission work, 1920-1921 (Box 78, Folder 2)
            - Congregational missions to Turkey, 1921 (Box 78, Folder 3)
            - Religious conditions in the Near East, 1922-1923 (Box 78, Folder 4)
            - Near East relief, 1922 (Box 78, Folder 5)
            - Problems of the Near East, 1922-1923 (Box 78, Folder 6)
            - The Turkish Treaty, 1926 (Box 78, Folder 6)
        - Carthage
          - Memoranda left by Edward Stoever, 1925 (Box 79, Folder 1)
          - Papers left by Edward Stoever, 1924-1925 (Box 79, Folder 2)
          - 1925 campaign, 1924-1925 (Box 79, Folder 3)
          - Kelsey articles, 1926 (Box 79, Folder 4)
          - Clippings and publicity, 1924-1925 (Box 79, Folder 5)
          - French, George. Plans, blueprints, 1926 (Box 79, Folder 6)
          - Gsell, S., 1926-1927 (Box 79, Folder 7)
          - Harden, D. B. Report. Quest of Punic vase types, 1926 (Box 79, Folder 8)
          - Merriam, John C, 1924-1926
            - 1924-1925 (Box 79, Folder 9)
            - 1926 (Box 79, Folder 10)
          - Ponssot, Louis, 1924-1925 (Box 80, Folder 1)
          - Stoever, Edward R., 1924-1926 (Box 80, Folder 2)
          - White, H. G. Evelyn. Re: Dimé dig, 1922-1925 (Box 80, Folder 3)
          - General Correspondence, 1924-1926 (Box 80, Folder 4)
          - Photos and prints, undated (Box 80, Folder 5)
          - Miscellaneous books and pamphlets, undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Papyri Collection
      - Transcribed Correspondence
        - Memo re: Papyri collection, 1915-1921 (Box 81, Folder 1)
        - 1921-1927, 3 folders (Box 81, Folder 2-4)
        - Memos and notes, 1923-1927 (Box 81, Folder 5)
        - Kelsey notes on Papyri, 1921-1923 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Papyri Correspondence
        - Anderson, John, 1922-1925 (Box 82, Folder 1)
        - Askren, David
          - Re: Freer Manuscript, 1915-1917; 1920-1921 (Box 82, Folder 2)
          - Miscellaneous
            - 1915, 1917-1919 (Box 82, Folder 3)
            - 1920-1921 (Box 82, Folder 4)
            - 1922-1923 (Box 82, Folder 5)
            - 1924, 6 folders (Box 82, Folder 6)
            - 1925 (Box 82, Folder 7)
            - 1926, 6 folders (Box 82, Folder 8)
            - 1927, 6 folders (Box 82, Folder 9)
        - Bell, H. Idris, 1920-1927
          - 1920-1921 (Box 82, Folder 10)
          - 1922-1924 (Box 82, Folder 11)
          - 1925-1927 (Box 82, Folder 12)
        - Bishop, William W., 1919-1927
          - 1919-1920 (Box 83, Folder 1)
          - 1921 (Box 83, Folder 2)
          - 1922 (Box 83, Folder 3)
          - 1923 (Box 83, Folder 4)
          - 1924-1925 (Box 83, Folder 5)
          - 1926-1927 (Box 83, Folder 6)
        - General Correspondence A-E, undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
        - Gejou, I. Elias
          - 1920, 1922 (Box 83, Folder 8)
          - 1923-1925 (Box 83, Folder 9)
        - Hunt, A. S., 1920-1926 (Box 84, Folder 1)
        - Kenyon, Frederick, 1920-1927
          - 1920-1922 (Box 84, Folder 2)
          - 1923-1924 (Box 84, Folder 3)
          - 1925-1927 (Box 84, Folder 4)
        - General Correspondence G-K, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
        - Lake, Kirsopp, 1923; 1925-1927 (Box 84, Folder 6)
        - Nahman, Maurice, 1920-1926
          - 1920-1921 (Box 84, Folder 7)
          - 1922-1923 (Box 84, Folder 8)
          - 1924-1926 (Box 84, Folder 9)
        - Voynich, Wilf~M., 1921-1927 (Box 84, Folder 10)
        - General Correspondence L-V, undated (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Inscriptions
      - Original Lot, Purchase and Shipment, 1899-1901 (Box 84a, Folder 1)
      - Dennison, Walter, 1899; 1909; 1916-1917 (Box 84a, Folder 2)
      - Professor Dennison's Publication, 1898 (Box 84a, Folder 3)
      - Etruscan Ash Urn Photos, 1909-1912 (Box 84a, Folder 4)
      - Sardis, etc., 1914-1915 (Box 84a, Folder 5)
      - Belgium, undated (Box 84a, Folder 6)
      - Cyrene, undated (Box 84a, Folder 7)
      - Mrs. Walter Dennison, 1917-1919 (Box 84a, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 84a, Folder 9)
      - Prospectus, undated (Box 84a, Folder 10)
      - Reprints, undated (Box 84a, Folder 11)
    - Frieze Diary (transcribed), 1855-1856
      - Pp. 1-100, 1855-1856 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Pp. 101-200, 1855- (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Pp. 201-300, 1856 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Pp. 301-300, 1856 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Pp. 301-312, 1856 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Appendix B., Letter of Charles Morris Smith to James B. Angell re: Professor Frieze as a traveling companion. (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Appendices C and D, letter to Orma Butler; index to diary (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Uncopied sheets, undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Belgian Relief Committee
      - Balance sheet and accounts, October 1914-September 30, 1920 (Box 86, Folder 1)
        (Forward by Herbert Hoover describes the background of the committee.)
      - Correspondence with individuals
        - Ann Arbor Steam & Dye Works, 1917-1920 (Box 86, Folder 2)
        - Baker, George Barr, 1917 (Box 86, Folder 3)
        - General Correspondence, 1917
          - B (Box 86, Folder 4)
          - C (Box 86, Folder 5)
          - D-G (Box 86, Folder 6)
          - H (Box 86, Folder 7)
          - I-O (Box 86, Folder 8)
        - Ottoway, E. J., 1917 (Box 86, Folder 9)
        - Sink, Charles A., 1917 (Box 86, Folder 10)
        - Sleeper, A. E., 1917 (Box 86, Folder 11)
        - General S-W Correspondence, 1917 (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - Committee Papers
        - Commission for Belgian Relief, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 1)
        - Executive Committee and State Committee, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 2)
        - Letters to State Committee, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 3)
        - Samples of letters and telegrams, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 4)
        - Maps, pamphlets, memoranda, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 5)
        - Lists from which addresses were taken, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 6)
        - Ann Arbor Committee, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 7)
        - Contributions-Expense fund; final report, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 8)
        - Contributions-lists, undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
        - Campus canvass, undated (Box 87, Folder 10)
        - Detroit Committee, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous funds, undated (Box 87, Folder 12)
        - Commission photographs, undated (Box 87, Folder 13)
        - Press notices, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 14)
        - Clippings, 1917 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Cities and Towns
        - Belgian-Relief Commission, 1917-1920; 1923 (Box 88, Folder 1)
        - Cities-A, 1917 (Box 88, Folder 2)
        - Ann Arbor, 1917 (Box 88, Folder 3)
        - Cities-B-C, 1917 (Box 88, Folder 4)
        - Detroit-A-L, 1917 (Box 88, Folder 5)
        - Detroit-M-Z, 1917 (Box 88, Folder 6)
        - Cities-D-F, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 1)
        - Cities-G-H, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 2)
        - Cities-I-L, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 3)
        - Cities-M-N, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 4)
        - Cities-O-R, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 5)
        - Cities-S-W, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 6)
        - Ypsilanti, 1917 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - Rotary Clubs
        - Miscellaneous, 1917 (Box 90, Folder 1)
        - Accounts, certified statements, 1917 (Box 90, Folder 2)
        - Bills paid, undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Publishers
    - Allyn & Bacon Boyer, Charles J.; Jones, John H., 1914; 1922-1924 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Allyn & Bacon Metcalf, R. A., 1918-1919 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - American Book Company Ambrose, Thomas, 1909; 1914-1915; 1918; 1922-1924; 1926 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - American Journal of Archaeology Elderkin, C. W., 1926 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Richard G. Badger Publishing Company, 1918-1919 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Classical Journal Miller, F. J., 1913-1919; 1923-1925 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - J. S. Cushing Company Barr, Oliver J., 1914-1927
      - 1914-1923 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - 1926-1927 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - J. S. Cushing Company re: Waterman volumes, 1922-1923 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Wilhem Engelmann, 1921-1922 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Macmillan & Company Brett, George B., 1912-1914; 1919; 1921-1924; 1926-1927 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Macmillan & Company Latham, H.S., 1913-1915; 1922 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Marsh, Edward C., 1913-1919; 4 folders (Box 91, Folder 2-5)
    - Miscellaneous items, 1913-1915; 1922-1924 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - National Fire Protection Association, 1922; 1925-1926 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - University of Chicago Press Mc Farland, A.C.
      - 1911-1917 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - 1908, 1910-1913 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Yale University Press Coleman, R. V.: Cooper, Lane, 1915-1916; 1918; 1922-1926 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Other Companies, 1904; 1913-1914; 1918-1926 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Re: Latin and Greek in American Education, 1916-1921 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Re: Richard Norton's book
      - Macmillan & Company Brett, George B., 1913-1918 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Brandegee, E. D., 1911-1916; 1922 (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Personal negotiations, 1913; 1916; 1922 (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Agreement; distribution, 1913-1915 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Manufacture: printing estimates, 1914 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Manufacture: engraving, 1912-1913 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Accounts, 1914-1915 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Data for new edition, 1914 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Bernini Sketches, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Half-tones, undated (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Loose plates and photos, undated; 2 folders (Box 92, Folder 11-12)
      - Notices and letters, 1914-1915 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Manuscripts
    - Hugo Grotius
      - Front matter, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Prolegomena, undated (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Book II: Chapters 2-19, undated; 18 folders (Box 93, Folder 3-20)
      - Book III: Notes and Chapters 6-17, undated (Box 93, Folder 21)
      - Book I
        - J. J. Reeves, undated (Box 93, Folder 22)
        - Chapters 3-4, undated (Box 93, Folder 23)
      - Book I returned by printer, undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - References, undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Epistle to Philemon, Paul V. Bacon, undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Epistle to Philemon, undated (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Finch, George A., 1919-1923 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - North, S. N. D. Law of War and Peace, 1918-1919 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Scott, James Brown War and Peace, 1918-1919 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Wright, Herbert F., 1918-1919 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Bills, undated (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - De Groot Bibliographical libraries, 1918-1919 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - De Groot memoranda, undated (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Earlier page proof, 1910 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Duplicate for printer, 1918 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Sample pages, undated (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - Loose items, 1919-1920 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Lanciani Destruction of Ancient Rome
      - Copy and proofs, 1899 (Box 95)
  - Printed Material
    - Ancient Life
      - Loose, miscellaneous items, undated (Box 96, Folder 1-2)
    - Caesar
      - Illustrations
        - Memoranda, undated (Box 96, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous items, undated (Box 96, Folder 4)
        - Berry-au-Bac, etc., undated (Box 96, Folder 5)
        - Used cuts, undated (Box 96, Folder 6)
        - Maps of Guischard, undated (Box 96, Folder 7)
        - Photographs-first expedition, undated (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Portraits
        - Res Gestae, Commentarii Historiae, undated (Box 97, Folder 1)